10/30/2018



hr@jiholee.me https://jiholee.me Los Angeles, CA (213) 935-7612





# **OBJECTIVE**

Full-stack developer from former designer. Experience designing and developing front-end and server-side small and large services. In a rapidly developing modern technology environment, always keep trying to learn and understand the flow of new technology. Regardless of platform, able to quickly learn and apply a variety of technologies.

## **TECHNIQUES**

#### Front-End

HTML5, CSS3, Saas, Less Javascript, ES6, TypeScript Bootstrap, Foundation JQuery, Vue.js, React,js

### **Back-End**

PHP, ASP, JSP, C#.NET, Laravel MSSQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL NoSQL: MongoDB, MariaDB Node.js, APIs, DevOps, Git, JIRA Cloud: AWS, Azure, GCP

#### **CMS**

WordPress, Drupal, Joomla!, XE3, WooCommerce, Magento, Orchard, Umbrac

### **Apps**

Swift, Object-C, Java, NW.js Cordova, CocoaPods, Xamarin Vue Native, React Native, Ionic

## **EXPERIENCE**

Nov 2010 - Present

**Freelancer** Developer
Los Angeles California

B2B e-commerce market place with CMS WordPress on AWS

Nov 2008 - Sep 2010

**Wewelcom** Web Developer Anyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea e-commerce solution ASP, MSSQL, API with SOAP and XML

Aug 2005 - Nov 2008

SEJONG Telecom (Ex. Onse Telecom) Web Developer Seongnam, Gyeonggi-do, Korea MRO IIS, ASP, MSSQL, Oracle, COM+ Sockets, MFC, C#.Net, Ajax Mar 2004 - Aug 2005 Assistant Engineer SI business, signal simulator, UI Design, PDA app, Mobile 2003

Jan 2002 - Mar 2004

**Seil I&C** Designer & Developer

Gwanak-gu, Seoul, Korea

Designed and Developed branding websites web apps on LAMP

### **EDUCATION**

Mar 2015 - Sep 2018

**Pacific States University**Bachelor of Science, C.I.S
Los Angeles California

Jan 2011 - Mar 2015

**Santa Monica College**AS, Computer Programming
Santa Monica California

Feb 2001 - Jan 2003

Hoseo University
Dropout, Information and
Telecommunication Engineering